<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jacob Delgado on Data Day(s) 2021</title>
    <link>/speakers/jacob-delgado/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jacob Delgado on Data Day(s) 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="/speakers/jacob-delgado/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Istio Product Security Working Group - What is it and why it’s important</title>
      <link>/sessions/istio-product-security-working-group-what-is-it-and-why-its-important/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sessions/istio-product-security-working-group-what-is-it-and-why-its-important/</guid>
      <description>The Istio Product Security Working Group operates behind a bit of secrecy given the nature of the group’s work; mostly triaging security reports and threats. In 2020, there were over 11 security bulletins released that spanned from Istio 1.3 to Istio 1.8. In this talk, we will explain why the group was created, how it operates, and its mission to make Istio more secure.
Namely, we will discuss:
 A brief history of how the group was formed Why it was necessary for the group to be created A look at Istio security vulnerabilities in 2020 How we triage security reports and fix them Pro-active measures the group is working on to make Istio more secure  Please join us to learn about the responsibilities of the Product Security Working Group and how to stay informed about the security of your environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Certificate Management (Using ECC Working Certificates)</title>
      <link>/sessions/simple-certificate-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sessions/simple-certificate-management/</guid>
      <description>There are numerous environmental variables that can be used to control the behavior of Istio. Environmental variables in Istio are considered experimental and there are no guarantees they won’t be removed in future versions of Istio.
In this talk, we will explore a few related to certificates used for inter-workload communication within your service mesh:
 Some of the pilot-agent environmental variables related to certificates How to toggle them during installation using istioctl and helm  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>